htmail.com 2017-06-06

# ZPOCK - Privacy Policy

ZPOCK.com is committed to user privacy in our products and services. This policy outlines our personal information handling practices. If you give us personal information, we will treat it according to this policy.

Zpok.com encourages you to read this privacy policy and those of all web sites you visit. Below is a summary of ZPOCK.com's online privacy policy.

#### Types and uses of personal information

Your personal information is used in the following ways:

  * Customer Feedback and Support. Provides a mechanism for requesting information from Fark. Also used to tell us how we can improve our products, services and site designs.
  * Email Correspondence. Used to raise and respond to issues and inquiries of all types. Also used to distribute information about Fark, our products, and services.
  * We will only use your personal information in the ways specified when it was collected. We will not subsequently change the way in which we use your personal information unless you consent to the new usage.

#### Security measures

We protect the personal information you share with us.

Authorized third party agents may also need access to some of your personal information. We only provide third party agents with the minimum amount of information needed to complete the requested service or transaction. We do not otherwise share your personal information with third parties unless you have granted us permission to do so.

#### Data Retention

ZPOCK.com will not retain your personal information longer than is necessary for the purposes for which it was collected.

#### Linked web sites

We provide links to third party sites. Since we do not control these Web sites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) third party sites.

#### Third Party Advertising

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. For more information on online behavioral advertising, privacy, cookies, and how this all works, please see the Network Advertising Initiative page on this topic.

#### Audience Analytics

In order to understand our audience, and understand how our audience interacts with ZPOCK.com, we use a few different analytics products. Each of these places a cookie on your computer to gather information about the pages you visit, how long you stay on the site, etc.

This information is aggregated so we can see general patterns. None of the information you provide on sign-up or while using the site is ever provided. One of these analytics products is Google Analytics.

#### Policy Updates

All updates to this policy will be posted here.

Note: This policy also covers the personal information you provide to ZPOCK.com Customer Support.
